(Hattori Maika) I'll tell Shun ➡
"We're going to break up."
♬〜
(Yugo)
Why do you go that far? ➡
I don't really want to break up.
I….
My relationship with my mother has always been
It's not that good...
I have no place to stay at home...
I was feeling suffocated.
So this is
It might be my ego though...
Just like me...
What makes Shun suffer about his family?
I don't like it.
Kato too
Isn't it tough?
What...
in front….
Any pain...
Once you get used to it, you won't feel anything
You said that, right?
♬〜
Before I could think about it like that...
I wonder how much he suffered.
There were brothers who could support each other...
If we could live together...
♬〜
The pain I have now...
I didn't have to feel it.
Why...➡
Why are you
Are you crying about us?
They were separated...
♬〜
It's not the two of them fault.
If it's true...
♬〜
Relying on each other...
I should have lived there.
♬〜
(Satotoshiｗｗ Recalling)
｟I'm in a difficult time...➡
At times like this
If there's a brother who can talk about anything ➡
How good it would be ➡
I've thought about it many times
Because it's
If you're suffering
I want to help ➡
Because it's family
♬〜
But I think so.
I can't change the past...
Because time is connected.
now
It's an extension of that time.
So if...
Just like me...
Kato too
If you felt lonely ➡
Even now, that loneliness
I think it can be changed.
Maybe I can change it.
of course.
♬〜
It really won't meet you.
Huh?
It's a bit tired of hating someone.
♬〜
📱(Manner mode)
Tap (Mobile operation sound)
hello.
thank you.
Clap... (applause)
I can work with you all ➡
I really think it was good.
Come here this job
I fell in love with it even more.
(Nozomi) Yes
Are you going to say that now? ➡
Don't go anymore!
(Everyone) Hahaha.
♬〜
(Yugo) Thank you so much. ➡
I'm fine even when I go back there.
yes.
♬〜
(Akiyama)
President Check this document.
How about me today?
(Akiyama) What... What...
As always, it's wonderful. ➡
Yeah.
Ou.
♬〜
Maika!
Shun-san!
♬〜
Welcome home.
I'm home.
♬〜
I got a call from Kato.
From my mother's plan
It seems like he's going to pull his hand.
That's good.
Thanks to Maika.
home. I have nothing...
If Maika is there ➡
I'm whatever
I feel like I can get over it.
from now on
Will you stay by your side forever?
of course.
Haha.
♬〜
Hmm...
good morning.
Do you have time this weekend?
About Maika to my parents
I want to introduce it properly.
yes.
♬〜
Huh? What about your dad?
(Mitsuko) That person won't come.
Huh?
(Photons)
Because I told you I didn't have to come.
Why, without permission...
(Photo) Of course. ➡
This is his precious time
It's stupid to use it.
(Photon) You too
Be aware of the president. ➡
What should you prioritize for the company?
If you think about it calmly, you'll understand, right? ➡
Marriage is
It's not just your own problem.
Really for the company
You do anything.
It also brought my brother closer to Maika
It's mom, isn't it?
He's (Photo) You knew. ➡
Did that girl talk?
No, I looked it up here.
(Photo) Whew... "I looked it up" ➡
That child
It's because he acted suspiciously.
It's really not available for a long time.
Um... why
Can you say that?
How did Kato feel?
Did you cooperate with your mother?
Can't you imagine it?
(Photo) No outsiders make a fuss.
Shun and Yugo are my children.
Listen to me
Of course.
My mother
No matter what you use to get in the way
I will live with Maika.
I can't imagine anything other than Maika.
(Photons)
There's no way I'll allow that.
I will make Shun happy.
Bang! (The sound of hitting the table)
Don't say anything stupid!
You're the opponent of Shun
I'm saying I can't work!
Mom! What a bit...
Are you okay?
⚞Gacha (door sound)
(Kenichi) Sorry I'm late.
Dad.
(Photo) Why...
(Kenichi) I thought this was
I came to check on it. ➡
Maika-san, sorry my wife. ➡
Are you injured?
yes.
(Kenichi)
I don't care about photons➡
She's a woman with a strong attitude.
Perfect for Shun.
Are you really saying it?
The future of the company is at stake!
(Kenichi) You married me ➡
What's important
Maybe you've lost sight of it?
Huh?
(Kenichi) What you're worried about is ➡
It's more of a pride than the future of the company.
Before you talk about the company
As a mother
Confront your son.
For the two
I want to introduce someone I love.
Hattori Maika is
He's the person I've decided on.
(Photons)
With such momentary emotions ➡
There's no way you can get married. ➡
This
A woman who is not a big family background ➡
I'm not worthy of being a wife of the president!
(Kenichi) Take care! ➡
How much damage to my sons
I feel satisfied. ➡
It's you who'll leave. ➡
Change your mind
Until I apologize to Shun properly ➡
Don't appear in front of me.
♬〜
(Kenichi) Maika
If you keep it, you'll catch a cold. Shun.
Ah
I'll prepare a change of clothes. let's go.
♬〜
(Photon) Wait.
How many I have ever been
Do you think you've done it all?
I'm glad I'm grateful!
No matter how hard it is, ➡
Gripping your teeth
I've climbed up to this point!
♬〜
I've done this much ➡
All of you
Please cooperate with my happiness!
ah~! Ah...
⚞Konkonkon (knokku)
yes.
Excuse me.
Shun-san, from your mother...
No... yet
It looks like he's not back at home either.
It's going to be another week.
⚞Kong Kong
president
We've found where Mitsuko is staying. ➡
At my affiliated hotel
Apparently they're staying there.
I see. thank you.
There's probably no place to go
I thought that was what it was like.
You're going to pick me up, right?
I've always been to that person
Maybe he wanted to get revenge.
Shun-san is
no matter how
Even if you're treated badly➡
To abandon is
You couldn't do it, did you?
That's after all➡
For Shun
Because he's an irreplaceable person.
♬〜
⚞Kong Kong
What's it for?
Properly
I want to talk to my mom.
If it stays like this ➡
We
Because you can't move forward.
Castella, mom, you liked it.
Why don't you all eat together?
♬〜
thank you.
(Yugo) Huh?
Come today.
If it was me, again
I think it was just an argument.
(Yugo) Hehe, I'm the same.
Hattori-san said this.
Time is connected.
The obvious thing
I've noticed it.
Depending on your own, family connections
You can change it.
I see.
Haha, that's good, we all met together.
thank you.
Yeah.
♬〜
I'm home.
welcome home.
With three
We've been talking slowly.
That's good.
Now finally
You can move towards marriage.
♬〜
That's what it is...
(Naomi)
fault? Maika alone? What about the CEO?
Shun-san hasn't come.
I'm going to come back ➡
I'll come with the president ➡
You'll be told about your marriage
I was thinking it.
That's what it is about...
We'll be doing it for a while ➡
Don't take the form of marriage
I want to live.
Huh?
Of course, what about Shun?
We're talking about staying together forever.
(Naomi) What are you talking about? ➡
Missing the timing
What should I do if I go late?
The woman is married and finally
Because you know the meaning of happiness.
I've always been
To that word from mom
I've been tied up but...
I finally understand.
That's not all.
What does that mean?
We will eventually
The choice of marriage
Maybe I will.
But that's ➡
We'll decide for ourselves.
What a stupid thing...
What is the president saying?
Mom ➡
I didn't choose the president.
I chose someone called Satori Shun.
Hey, do you remember?
I was friends when I was a student.
About Kagaya-kun.
Huh?
Mom is coming
Throw away the book you lent me ➡
I don't want to talk about it
I said something terrible ➡
That Kagaya-kun is ➡
He's my first love.
Why isn't that relevant now...
Satori Shun is ➡
It's Kagaya-kun.
Huh?
I was able to meet Shun again ➡
I really think it was good.
♬〜
That's all I wanted to convey.
What mom says
If you listen ➡
I could be happy though.
Mom ➡
I'm happy enough now.
♬〜
Gacha slack (door sound)
Pee Pee Pee... (bird's cry)
Lady
It's going to get dark soon.
Shun-san, why?
From Maika's mother
I got a call.
About Maika
thank you⦆
｟📱 Of course｠
｟Because that girl looks like me ➡
I'm worried
Mom...
"She looks like me"
Did you say it?
ah.
That's it...
It's not similar at all.
About someone you love ➡
Anyway, I have a sense of cherishment ➡
Does it mean that you're strong?
♬〜
Mom is
I was happy to get married soon➡
To my beloved daughter
I want you to live the same way➡
I think he thought so.
But that
It was a burden for Maika.
I've noticed it.
that's why
Please go out of your way to contact me ➡
Thank you very much
I think he said that.
The important person can't understand
It's painful to think about it though ➡
If you want to understand it ➡
I think the distance will be closer.
♬〜
I agree.
Shun-san.
yeah?
My selfishness...
Please listen
thank you.
Marriage is
It's not something to decide in a hurry.
Let's talk slowly.
Because there's a lot of time.
I agree.
♬〜
It's been 12 years since then➡
Also
I was supported by Shun.
Even 12 years from now ➡
I'll support Maika.
thank you.
Me too ➡
Forever forever
I want to help Shun.
Yeah.
♬〜
Shun-san.
yeah?
♬〜
More than then ➡
I like you.
♬〜
It's me too.